flightmapper.net 2017-11-20

# Privacy policy

At FlightMapper.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. 

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit FlightMapper.net. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use third party advertisements on FlightMapper.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site).   
DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. 

### Google App Engine

Parts of the FlightMapper.net website are hosted on Google App Engine, thus the privacy policy of Google App Engine also applies on this website. You can read the Google App Engine privacy policy by visiting: [ http://code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html ](http://code.google.com/appengine/privacy.html)

### Google Analytics

The FlightMapper.net website uses Google Analytics for usage statistics collection, thus the privacy policy of Google Analytics also applies on this website. Learn more by visiting: [ http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)
